bruce-juice.com 2012-10-10

# Bruce Juice Privacy Notice

###### Last updated: 12.02.2011

##### bruce-juice.com respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it at all times. This Internet Privacy Notice explains how we collect, use, and safeguard information on this web site. Please read this Privacy Notice carefully. **By visiting bruce-juice.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice and agree that any dispute over privacy is governed by this Privacy Notice and Conditions of Use.**

##### By continuing to use the bruce-juice.com web site. after we post any changes to this Privacy Notice, you accept the Privacy Notice as modified.

#### **What Personal Information About visitors does bruce-juice.com and it's 3rd party services collect?**

#### **Information You Give Us:**

##### We receive and store any personal and financial information you enter on our web site. or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future options for you, improving our web site, and communicating with you.

#### **Automatic Information:**

##### bruce-juice.com and 3rd party services on bruce-juice.com receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the site. For example, the use of "cookies," and the obtainment of certain types of information when your web browser accesses bruce-juice.com and 3rd party services on bruce-juice.com, including your IP address. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at bruce-juice.com, if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.

#### **E-mail Communications:**

##### To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from @brucejuice.co.uk if your computer supports such capabilities.

#### **What About Cookies?**

##### Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we and 3rd party services transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems and 3rd party services to recognize your browser and to provide features such as personalised advertisements and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.

##### The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of bruce-juices.com's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

#### **Does bruce-juice.com Share The Information It Receives?**

##### Information about our visitors is an important part of our future development but we are not in the business of selling or sharing it to others. We share customer information only as described below.

#### **Third-Party Service Providers**

##### We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending e-mails, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

#### **Business Transfers**

##### As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, domains, web sites, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that bruce-juice.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

#### **Protection of bruce-juice.com and Others**

##### We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of bruce-juice.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.

#### **With Your Consent**

##### Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

#### **What Information Can I Access?**

##### bruce-juice.com does not supply public access to the information and statistics we hold. We are by law obligated to supply such information we may keep about your individual usage of bruce-juice.com. **We are not responsible for the information on 3rd party services, we are however obligated to supply information on these services, which you would then need to approach individually.**

#### **Are Children Allowed To Use bruce-juice.com?**

##### Some content and 3rd party content on bruce-juice.com **IS NOT** suitable for children, bruce-juice.com does not host and supply porn or x-rated material and is therefore not filtered or blocked when using parental control and filtering software.

##### This website is targeted at the UK and Northern Ireland, Although bruce-juice.com is available world wide and receives global visitors, when referring to adult content bruce-juice.com uses British standards. Content found on bruce-juice.com, in the UK and Northern Ireland would be given an age approval rating of 15 years old and above,

#### **Conditions Of Use, Notices, And Revisions**

##### If you choose to visit bruce-juice.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this notice and our conditions of use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the United Kingdom. If you have any concern about privacy at bruce-juice.com, please contact us at 'privacy@brucejuice.co.uk' with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

##### Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
